[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "If you don’t hurry, ___we get to the stop, the bus will have left.",
        "answer": "by the time"
    },
    {
        "question": "Some people think islands like Penghu will have disappeared ___.",
        "answer": "in eighty years"
    },
    {
        "question": "It looks like we ___ different weather patterns in the future.",
        "answer": "will be having"
    },
    {
        "question": "We’ll be having that big meeting ___. You had better be prepared!",
        "answer": "in a few days"
    },
    {
        "question": "___, she will have written five reports.",
        "answer": "By the end of May"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hopefully, you will have recovered ___ I see you.",
        "answer": "by the next time"
    },
    {
        "question": "I probably ___ the assignment by this coming Friday.",
        "answer": "won’t have finished"
    },
    {
        "question": "By this time tomorrow, we ___ over the Pacific Ocean to Canada.",
        "answer": "will be flying"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ken ___ for Japan by next Saturday.",
        "answer": "will have already left"
    },
    {
        "question": "They will be in a meeting ___.",
        "answer": "between 2:00 p.m. and 3:00 p.m."
    },
    {
        "question": "She ___ enough money until at least early next year.",
        "answer": "won’t have saved"
    },
    {
        "question": "Will they be coming with us to see a movie ___?",
        "answer": "tonight"
    },
    {
        "question": "He will have learned enough Japanese to go to Japan ___.",
        "answer": "in a few months"
    },
    {
        "question": "We will have finished all our tests ___.",
        "answer": "by Friday"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can borrow my car tomorrow. I ___ it then.",
        "answer": "won’t be using"
    },
    {
        "question": "They say the extreme weather conditions ___ by the middle of the century.",
        "answer": "will have worsened"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where ___ this holiday weekend?",
        "answer": "will you be going"
    }
]